Guide to the Bob Fitch Photography Archive M1994
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Subject Files, 1960-2016; 23 Linear Feet 43 manuscript boxes
  - United Auto Workers: Convention, Los Angeles, California [contact sheets], June, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    United Automobile Workers conference with union officials including Leonard Woodcock and Douglas Fraser and special speakers including Jacque Cousteau, Cesar Chavez and President Jimmy Carter, Los Angeles, California, photographed by Bob Fitch.
    Contact sheets are numbered 4459, 4460, 4462-4483, 4513, 4514.
  - United Auto Workers: Portland, Oregon [contact sheets], May 8, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    Contact sheets are numbered 5676-5684.
  - United Auto Workers: Meeting with Jimmy Carter, June, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    Prints are numbered 4474, 4490.
  - United Church of Christ: Non-violence training [contact sheets], 1971 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3235-3245.
  - United Church of Christ: Youth solstice, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    Contact sheets are numbered 276-281, 283, 287, 289.
  - United Mine Workers: Picketing at Belle Ayr and Wyodak Mines near Gilette, Wyoming [contact sheets], June, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4399, 4401-4406.
  - University Lutheran Chapel, Berkeley, California [contact sheets], November, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3172-3175, 3212.
  - University of California Santa Cruz: Career fair/military recruiters, Santa Cruz, California [printed contact sheets], April 5, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Valarie: Squatter in abandoned building [contact sheets], May, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3381-3387.
  - Van Pelt, Dale [contact sheets], 1968 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    Contact sheet is numbered 573.
  - Vancouver Folk Song Society: Folk camp, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada [contact sheets], July, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    Contact sheets are numbered 5788, 5791, 5795.
  - Veterans Day parade, Hayward, California [contact sheets], 1971 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3121-3125, 3127, 3128.
  - Veterans protest [prints], 1971 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    Prints are numbered 3234.
  - Vietnam trip [contact sheets, notes and prints], 2004 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    Contact sheets are numbered 6208-6227.
  - Vietnam trip: Notes, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Photo identifications, 2014 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Burning Christmas tree during a demonstration [contact sheets], December, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    Contact sheet is numbered 3234.
  - Voter registration, Santa Cruz, California [contact sheets], 2004 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    Contact sheet is numbered 6112.
  - Waldorf School, Santa Cruz, California [contact sheets], May 1, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    Contact sheets are numbered 6136, 6160, 6161.
  - Walton birthday [contact sheets], March, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1653, 1654, 1656-1658.
  - War Resisters League: 50th Anniversary at Asilomar, California [contact sheets], August 5, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    War Resister's League 50th anniversary event, with Joan Baez, Daniel Ellsberg, A.J. Muste, Lee Swenson, Carol Swenson, David McReynolds, Igal Roodenko and others, Asilomar, California.
    Contact sheets are numbered 3932, 3934-3942.
  - War Resisters League: 50th Anniversary at Asilomar, California [slides], August 5, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Ward, Mark: Student at Claremont Junior High School potential prospect for a Bob Fitch book [contact sheets and notes], 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2021, 2333, 2334-2344, 2367, 2368, 2376, 2378, 2402-2411, 2423, 2425, 2426, 2471-2484, 2628, 2630, 2632-2636, 2852, 2858, 2860, 2863, 2864, 2876, 2906, 2916, 2921.
    The book created from these images, Mark Will Ward: a Black family in the city has been scanned and digitized and can be viewed through this link:
    https://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/10457955
  - Washoe, Tina, Taylorsville, California [contact sheets and notes], October, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    Contact sheets are numbered 5554-5562, 5571, 5577.
  - Watsonville, California: Graveyard [contact sheets], 1975 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4397.
  - Wedding: Tom and Abeja [program], June 17, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Wedding party [contact sheets], January, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    Contact sheet is numbered 3627.
  - Weed, California: Little League All-Star team [prints and negatives], 1980 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Weed, California: Carnivale [contact sheets], August, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4534.
  - Weed, California: Carnivale [contact sheets], September, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    Contact sheet is numbered 5624, 5626.
  - Weed, California: Elementary school cheer leaders [negatives], 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Weed, California: Elementary school trip to Castle Crags [contact sheets], May, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    Contact sheets are numbered 5607, 5608.
  - Weed, California: Elementary school trip to Castle Crags [slides], May, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Weed, California: Friends [contact sheets and notes], 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4509, 5512.
  - Weed, California [slides], 1981-1982 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - West Oakland Parish, Oakland, California [contact sheets], 1966-1967 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    Contact sheets are numbered 189, 190.
  - Westbrook, Yvonne: Campaign for City Supervisor, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], 1971 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3133, 3134, 3136, 3138, 3140, 3142, 3146-3152.
  - Westbrook, Yvonne: Election day [contact sheets], November 2, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3154, 3156-3171.
  - Westbrook, Yvonne [slides], 1972 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Whatchamacallit: San Francisco Bay Area television program for youth on KPIX [contact sheets], January, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    Meetings and production for Whatchamacallit, a television program for youth broadcast on KPIX, San Francisco, California.
    Contact sheets are numbered 3632-3637, 3642-3657.
  - Wheat field [contact sheets], 1971 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    Contact sheet is numbered 2822.
  - Wheelers Ranch Commune near Occidental, California [contact sheets], 1969-1970 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Contact sheets are numbered 987, 996, 1001, 1002, 1008-1050, 1052, 1054-1083.
  - Wheelers Ranch Commune near Occidental, California [contact sheets], 1969-1970 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1085-1089, 1091-1106, 1108-1117, 1119-1122, 1124-1127, 1129-1136.
  - Wheelers Ranch Commune near Occidental, California [contact sheets], 1969-1970 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1138-1157, 1180, 1183, 1187, 1191, 1193, 1195, 1199, 1203, 1206-1209, 1217-1226, 1229-1233, 1235, 1630, 1631, 1633.
  - Wheelers Ranch Commune: Bryce and Charlotte, near Occidental, California [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1170, 1172, 1176-1179, 1181, 1182, 1184-1186, 1188-1190, 1192, 1194, 1196, 1197, 1198, 1200, 1201, 1202, 1204, 1205, 1210-1215, 1228.
  - Wheelers Ranch Commune, near Occidental, California [prints], 1969-1970 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    Prints are numbered 822, 987, 1119, 1122-1124, 1126, 1127.
  - Wheelers Ranch Commune, near Occidental, California [slides] [part 1 of 2], 1969-1970 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Wheelers Ranch Commune, near Occidental, California [slides] [part 2 of 2], 1969-1970 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Whipple, Todd, Yreka, California [contact sheets and notes], October, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    Contact sheets are numbered 5518, 5563, 5564, 5570, 5572-5574, 5576, 5578, 5579.
  - White defense [contact sheets], 1967 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    Contact sheets are numbered 512, 513.
  - Widener, Warren, Berkeley, California [contact sheets], April 23, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3002-3004.
  - Widener, Warren [slides], 1970 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Widener, Warren [contact sheets], 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2443-2445, 2451, 2453-2455, 2490, 2491, 2547, 2731-2734.
  - Widener, Warren: Installation as Berkeley Mayor, Berkeley, California [contact sheets], May 4, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2788, 2789, 2791, 2794.
  - Widener, Warren [copy negatives], 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Widener, Warren and family [contact sheets], 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2445, 2490, 2491, 2493, 2529, 2530, 2549, 2603, 2605, 2610, 2644.
  - Williams, Hosea [contact sheets], 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    Contact sheets are numbered 161, 180.
  - Williams, Joe: Peace and Freedom candidate for Congress [contact sheets], August 22, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    Contact sheets are numbered 6186-6188.
  - Williamson family [contact sheets], 1973 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3532, 3533.
  - Wilson, Holly [contact sheets], February, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    Contact sheet is numbered 1629.
  - Women [part 1 of 2] [prints], 1960-2016 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    Prints are numbered 235, 237, 258, 288, 296, 379, 704, 924, 1158, 1159, 1224, 1889, 2096, 3865, 2908, 3176, 3228, 3256, 3265, 3283, 3323, 3324, 3394, 3420, 3423, 3498, 3499, 3524-3526, 3529, 3554, 3556, 3564, 3578, 3579, 3614-3616, 3622, 3751, 3755, 3764, 3739, 3784, 3877, 4091, 4124, 4132, 4136, 4288, 4301, 4382, 4413, 4426, 4520, 4575.
  - Women [part 2 of 2] [prints], 1960-2016 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Women friends [contact sheets], 1973 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3735, 3736.
  - Woody [contact sheets], 1968 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    Contact sheets are numbered 626-629.
  - Work [prints], 1966-1978 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    Prints are numbered 110, 377, 704, 1607, 1848, 2970, 3358, 3394, 3398, 3399, 3589, 3617, 3622, 3692, 4915.
  - Work: Housing and Community Development [prints], 1990-1995 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    Prints are numbered 5786, 5840, 5846, 5848, 5882.
  - Working Susan [contact sheets], November, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    Contact sheet is numbered 3176.
  - Yosemite, California [contact sheets], 1976 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4525, 4526.
  - Young Men's Christian Association dance, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    Contact sheets are numbered 946, 947, 949, 951-954.
  - Z - [contact sheets] [RESTRICTED], November, 1973 (Box 135, Folder 9)
    Materials in this file are restricted until January 1, 2063.
    Contact sheets are numbered 4070, 4091.
  - Zeeman, Sue and Bob [contact sheets], June 12, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    Contact sheet is numbered 6175.
  - Zimmerman, Charlie [contact sheets], February 14, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Zwirn, Bari [prints], 1993 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    Prints are numbered 5836, 5837.
  - Zwirn, Bari [prints], 1993 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    Prints are numbered 5828, 5837-5839.
- Series 2: Classics, 1965-2013
  Contains mostly photographic materials: contact sheets, prints, negatives and slides. Additionally there is a small amount of correspondence, newspaper clippings, research materials and notes. Many of the images in this series either duplicate, overlap, or complement materials in other series. Additional related images may be found in other series.
  Biographical
  This series is composed of some of the most iconic and frequently requested images that Bob Fitch captured, including Martin Luther King Jr., the Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear and the civil rights movement, Cesar Chavez and the farm workers movement, Dorothy Day, and Joan Baez and David Harris. Fitch had many copies of high-quality prints for some of the images in this series.
  Bob Fitch separated the materials in this series and the series is arranged in original order. The numbers preceding the folder titles are Fitch's numbered filing system.
  - Fitch 4450: Farmworker's hands, Calexico, California [prints and negatives], 1976 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 725: Daniel Berrigan Peace Fingers, Catonsville Nine Trial, Federal Courthouse, Baltimore, Maryland [contact sheets, prints and negatives], 1969 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Father Daniel Berrigan making the peace sign with his fingers while handcuffed during the Catonsville 9 trial at the Federal Courthouse, Baltimore, Maryland. Includes prints and negatives.
  - Fitch 423: "Peace Fingers" draft protesters being arrested, Army Induction Center, Oakland, California [prints and negatives], 1967 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 5999: "Palestine Hands" holding a key, Jerusalem, Israel [prints and negatives], 2004 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 1333: David Harris and Joan Baez at their Struggle Mountain home, Los Altos Hills, California [prints and negatives], 1969 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 1414: Pete Seeger, Clearwater Sloop Festival, Kingston, New York [prints and negatives], 1969 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 994: Hippies Is Necessary "Huggers", Haight Theatre, San Francisco, California [prints and negatives], 1969 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 3895: Dorothy Day sitting on a stool at a United Farm Workers picket, Lamont, California [prints and negatives], August 1, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 1402: Cesar Chavez portrait, Delano, California [prints and negatives], 1969 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 2102: Farmworker with a short hoe in celery field, Salinas, California [prints and negatives], 1970 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Cesar Chavez Stamp, Filipino Hall, Delano, California [prints], 1970 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Photos taken by Cesar Chavez on East Coast and Canada Tour [negatives], 1969 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - United Farm Workers: Cesar Chavez East Coast and Canada Tour [prints and copy negatives], 1969 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - United Farm Workers Organizing Committee, Delano, California [copy negatives], 1968-1970 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 2046: Armed guard "protecting" replacement workers from United Farm Workers pickets and organizers in lettuce field, Salinas, California [prints], 1970 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - SCLC 125: Dorinda Palmer leading marchers to City Hall, blocked by sheriffs and deputized civilians, Greenwood, Mississippi [prints and negatives], 1965 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - SCLC 146: Voter registration mobile, Montgomery, Alabama [negatives], 1965 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - SCLC 148: Sheriff Bill Lee slapping Tom Gilmore during a march to integrate schools, Eutaw, Alabama [prints and negatives], 1965, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - SCLC 168: Martin Luther King Jr., preaching, Eutaw, Alabama [contact sheets and negatives], 1965 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - SCLC 210: Black American Gothic, Mr. and Mrs. Roz Heinz, Camden, Alabama [contact sheets, prints and negatives], 1965 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Photograph Bob Fitch titled "Black American Gothic": Mr. and Mrs. Roz Heinz in their home grieving her brother, David Colston, who was shot and killed by a white farmer after a traffic accident, Camden, Alabama. Also includes images of David Colston's corpse and article about the killing.
  - SCLC 229: Woman in front of a burnt house, Birmingham, Alabama [prints and negatives], 1965-1966 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - SCLC 254: Martin Luther King Jr., playing pool, Chicago, Illinois [contact sheets, prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - SCLC 354: Schoolroom, Alabama [prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - SCLC 392: Girl holding a broken transistor radio, Camden, Alabama [prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - SCLC 459: Martin Luther King Jr. walking in the rain and greeting supporters, Gadsden, Alabama [prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - SCLC 474: Martin Luther King Jr. preaching at pulpit with attentive boy next to him, Eutaw, Alabama [prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - SCLC 484: Martin Luther King Jr. with Fred Shuttlesworth, Bernard Lee, and Hosea Williams, Kelly Ingram Park, Birmingham, Alabama [prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - SCLC 487A: Martin Luther King Jr. with his children during voter registration drive, Kelly Ingram Park, Birmingham, Alabama [negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - SCLC 487B: Martin Luther King Jr. with his children and Richard Smiley during voter registration drive, Kelly Ingram Park, Birmingham, Alabama [negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - SCLC 496: Martin Luther King Jr. speaking at Brown Chapel, Selma, Alabama [negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - SCLC 529: Lucius Amerson, candidate for Macon County Sheriff, Alabama [contact sheets, prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - SCLC 568: El Fondren - 100 year old man registering to vote, Batesville, Mississippi [prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - El Fondren family source material, 1966-2013 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - El Fondren family reunion t-shirt, 2013 (Box 132, Item 2)
    Two off-white t-shirts from Fondren family reunion with Bob Fitch's photograph of El Fondren celebrating registering to vote for the first time in his life on the front of the shirt.
  - SCLC 569: Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear - marchers passing and waving to farmworkers on a tractor, Mississippi [prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - SCLC 592: Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear - marchers ringing a church bell, Mississippi [prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - SCLC 596: Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear - Martin Luther King Jr. resting during a break surrounded by press and supporters, shaking hands with Annie Devine, Canton, Mississippi [prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - SCLC 604: Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear - Floyd McKissick, Martin Luther King Jr. and Stokely Carmichael walking together, Mississippi [contact sheets, prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - SCLC 636: Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear - Stokely Carmichael speaking on a flatbed truck during a nighttime rally, first public use of the phrase "black power", Canton, Mississippi [prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - SCLC 654: Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear - marcher holding large button, Jackson, Mississippi [prints and negatives], June 26, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - SCLC 655: Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear - Martin Luther King Jr. with Coretta Scott King, Ralph Abernathy, Juanita Abernathy, Floyd McKissick and Stokely Carmichael leading marchers entering Jackson, Mississippi [contact sheets, prints and negatives], June 26, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - SCLC 661: Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear - Martin Luther King Jr. and Andrew Young march past a state highway patrol officer, Philadelphia, Mississippi [prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - SCLC 686: Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear - Martin Luther King Jr., Bernard Lee, Andrew Young, Robert Green, Lawrence Guyot and Stokely Carmichael discuss "black power" slogan, Canton, Mississippi [contact sheets, prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - SCLC 721: Man holding "Downtown Will Need Us…." sign, Grenada, Mississippi [negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - SCLC 798: Martin Luther King Jr., Joan Baez, Hosea Williams and Andrew Young walking with schoolchildren during a march to integrate schools, Grenada, Mississippi [prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - SCLC 825: Martin Luther King Jr. and Andrew Young sitting and waiting in an airport terminal, Montgomery, Alabama [prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - SCLC 932: Septima Clark guiding the hand of a Citizen Education Program student during SCLC's Voter Education Project, Camden, Alabama [prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - SCLC 968: Martin Luther King Jr. standing in his office in front of a portrait of Mahatma Gandhi, Atlanta, Georgia [prints and negatives], 1967 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Memorial: Correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 4349: Martin Luther King Jr.'s casket during funeral, Atlanta, Georgia [negatives], April 9, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 4355: Martin Luther King Sr. and Alberta Williams King during Martin Luther King Jr.'s funeral, Atlanta, Georgia [contact sheets, prints and negatives], April 9, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Martin Luther King Jr.'s funeral, Atlanta, Georgia [prints], April 9, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 514: Coretta Scott King during Martin Luther King Jr.'s funeral, Atlanta, Georgia [print and slide], April 9, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Coretta Scott King comforts her daughter Bernice King during Martin Luther King Jr.'s funeral, Atlanta, Georgia [prints and slides], April 9, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. family Christmas card [prints and negatives], 1966 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 4363: Rosa Parks [prints and negatives], January, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 1285: Greene County housing co-operative, Eutaw, Alabama [contact sheets and negatives], 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Black Panther Party office with bullet holes, Oakland, California [copy negatives], 1968 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Miscellaneous [contact sheets], 1966-1968 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Coretta Scott King with Ron Dellums' congressional campaign, Oakland, California [copy negatives], 1970 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Mosaic of Bob Fitch's photographs from the South, 1966-1968 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Ron Dellums [prints and copy negatives], 1968-1973 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Ralph Abernathy [prints and copy negatives], 1966-1968 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Series 3: Glide Foundation/Glide Methodist Memorial Church, 1964-1973
  Contains mostly photographic materials: contact sheets, prints, negatives and slides. Additionally there is a small amount of correspondence, newspaper clippings and notes. There are images related to this series in Series 1: Subject Files, Series 2: Classics, Series 6: Black Star Agency, and Series 9: Computer Media/Digital Materials.
  The materials in this series document Bob Fitch's work and involvement with the Glide Foundation and the Glide Memorial Methodist Church in San Francisco. Following his graduation from the Pacific School of Religion, Fitch worked for the Glide Foundation as a community organizer and photographer for youth and homeless groups. He later continued to do freelance work and to document events at Glide Memorial Methodist Church.
  This series is arranged in original order chronologically.
  - Glide Foundation: Contact sheets 101-130, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Glide Foundation: Contact sheets 131-150, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Glide Foundation: Contact sheets 151-170, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Glide Foundation: Contact sheets 171-190, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Glide Foundation: Contact sheets 191-220, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Glide Foundation: Contact sheets 221-238, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Glide Foundation: Contact sheets 241-260, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Glide Foundation: Contact sheets 261-280, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Glide Foundation: Contact sheets 282-300, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Glide Foundation: Contact sheets 301-320, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Glide Foundation: Contact sheets 321-340, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Glide Foundation: Contact sheets 341-377, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Glide Foundation: Contact sheets 380-382, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church, San Francisco, California [contact sheets and notes], 1966-1968 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    Contact sheets are numbered 170, 171, 192, 193, 196-198, 201-205, 207, 301, 436.
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church: Staff, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], 1966-1973 (Box 44, Folder 12)